great news everyone you may not shop all
night for your life insurance needs
we all need extra protection today every
day
so whether you are currently at work
staying or running errands make sure you
spare a few minutes
to get insured our fwd plans are
available online
24x7 for everyone aged 18
to 50. now let's take a look at an
example of getting a critical illness
coverage
using our fwd online shop
let's see how
[Music]
visit bitly slash get set for health
click on get a quote to start creating
the proposal
provide your personal information such
as gender and birth date
select the amount of protection coverage
you need minimum of 500
000 and maximum of 1 million click next
two proposals will be shown 5-year pay
period and 10-year pay period
you may choose the premium payment
frequency quarterly
semi-annual or annual click accept and
proceed to continue with the application
click next two proposals will be shown
five-year pay period and 10-year pay
period you may choose the premium
payment frequency
quarterly semi-annual or annual click
accept and proceed to continue with the
application
read through the important reminders
such as the list of valid ids
before proceeding to the next step and
starting your application
on the application form provide your
personal information such as citizenship
country occupation business address
home address and valid id
answer the health and medical questions
as part of your health declaration
choose your preferred pay period 5 years
or 10 years
decide on the premium payment frequency
quarterly
semi-annual or annual
read through the summary of benefits and
confirm payment at the bottom of the
page
the page will be redirected to the
payment portal
please choose credit slash debit card or
gcash to initiate payment
congratulations upon successful payment
your policy will be instantly issued
[Music]
you